Finding Aid for the George Alexander Heard Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- (La-Mi)
  - Magill, Robert N (Box 7)
  - Magill, Samauel H (Box 7)
  - Haes, Ernest E (Box 7)
  - Malin, Patrick Murphy (Box 7)
  - Mann, W.R (Box 7)
  - Mansfield, Harvey C (Box 7)
  - Mansfield, Mike (Box 7)
  - Marburger, Harold J (Box 7)
  - Markham, E.C (Box 7)
  - A.N. Marquis Company (Box 7)
  - Marr, Lawrence N (Box 7)
  - Martin, Betty Maclean (Box 7)
  - Martin, Joseph W., Jr (Box 7)
  - Martin, Roscoe C (Box 7)
  - Martin, Roscoe C (Box 7)
  - Martin, Roscoe C (Box 7)
  - Martin, Roscoe C. (TVA Project Luncheon) (Box 7)
  - Martinez, Pete (Box 7)
  - Marts, A.C (Box 7)
  - Marrick, Dwaine (Box 7)
  - Maryland, University of (Box 7)
  - Marx, Alexander (Box 7)
  - Mattman, Alfred G (Box 7)
  - McBroom, James Thomas (Box 7)
  - McCaffree, Floyd E (Box 7)
  - McCallister, Frank (Box 7)
  - McCleery, Richard H (Box 7)
  - McCormick, George Dectar (Box 7)
  - McCormick, Katranita (Box 7)
  - McDonald, Bob (Box 7)
  - McDonald, Neil A (Box 7)
  - McEwen, J.H. Mrs (Box 7)
  - McGee, Fred (Box 7)
  - McGehee, Edward (Box 7)
  - McGlinn, Frank C.P (Box 7)
  - McHenry, Dean E (Box 7)
  - McIntire, Lucy B (Box 7)
  - McIntosh, C.E (Box 7)
  - McIntosh, C.J (Box 7)
  - McKean, Dayton D (Box 7)
  - McKee, Don (Box 7)
  - McKee, Mary (Box 7)
  - McKee, J.T (Box 7)
  - McKinley, Charles (Box 7)
  - McKnight, Margaret H (Box 7)
  - McKnight, Pete (Box 7)
  - McLain, George (Box 7)
  - McLean, Joseph E (Box 7)
  - McMahon, Alex (Box 7)
  - McMath, Sidney S (Box 7)
  - McMillan, George (Box 7)
  - McNeel Memorials (Box 7)
  - McWilliams, Carey (Box 7)
  - Meade, Robert D (Box 7)
  - Meek, Josephine T (Box 7)
  - Mendelson, Wallace (Box 7)
  - Merriam, Robert E (Box 7)
  - Merzbacher, Eugene (Box 7)
  - Metger, Phil (Box 7)
  - Michel, John D (Box 7)
  - Mickey, Paul (Box 7)
  - Milbrath, Lester W (Box 7)
  - Milbrath, Lester W (Box 7)
  - Miller, Francis P (Box 7)
  - Miller, Helen Hill (Box 7)
  - Miller, Samuel (Box 7)
  - Miller, Warrne E (Box 7)
  - Millett, John D (Box 7)
  - Milner, Charles (Box 7)
  - Milwaukee Journal, The (Box 7)
  - Misheloff, Ruth (Box 7)
- (Mi-Ri)
  - Mitchell, George (Box 8)
  - Monroe, John (Box 8)
  - Moon, Henry Lee (Box 8)
  - Moore, Albert Cunningham (Box 8)
  - Moore, Edward F (Box 8)
  - Moore, Harry T (Box 8)
  - Moos, Malcolm (Box 8)
  - Morrison, David J (Box 8)
  - Morton, Edward Taylor Mrs (Box 8)
  - Moses, Percival Sneed (Box 8)
  - Mott, Paul (Box 8)
  - Muller, Fred (Box 8)
  - Mund, Vernon A (Box 8)
  - Mundt, Karl E (Box 8)
  - Munger, Frank (Box 8)
  - Murra, John Victor (Box 8)
  - Muschamp, E.A (Box 8)
  - Musgrove, Downing (Box 8)
  - M's Miscellaneous (Bureau of Public Administration) (Box 8)
  - Nam, Charles (Box 8)
  - Nash, Arturo (Box 8)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Box 8)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress (Box 8)
  - National Institute of Public Affairs (Box 8)
  - National Planning Association (Box 8)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, Inc (Box 8)
  - Naval Papers (Box 8)
  - Naval Reserve Officers Training Corps (Box 8)
  - Navy - Inactive Duty (Box 8)
  - Naval Reserve U.S (Box 8)
  - Negro Suffrage (Box 8)
  - Neiman, Ernest (Box 8)
  - Nester, Alfred T (Box 8)
  - Neuberger, Richard L (Box 8)
  - Neumann: Modern Political Parties (Box 8)
  - New York City Photos (Box 8)
  - Nicholson, George (Box 8)
  - Nigrelli, H (Box 8)
  - Noble, Wesley (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Republican Correspondence (Box 8)
  - North Carolina & University of North Carolina (Box 8)
  - Norton, E.B (Box 8)
  - The North Carolina Historical Review, Vol.XXVII, No.1, October 4, 1950 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous (One Photograph, One Picture, Correspondence, Article, Newspaper Clippings) (Box 8)
  - Odegard, Peter H (Box 8)
  - Odum, Howard W (Box 8)
  - Ogburn, Charlton (Box 8)
  - Oil Industry Information Committee (Box 8)
  - Olden, Samuel B (Box 8)
  - Oppegaard, Harry E (Box 8)
  - Ostrom, Vincent A (Box 8)
  - Overacker, Louise (Box 8)
  - Owens, John (Box 8)
  - Pacific Ocean Area (Box 8)
  - Page, Owen H., Jr (Box 8)
  - Pauley, Edwin W (Box 8)
  - Palmer, Dwight R.G (Box 8)
  - Pannell, Anne Gary (Box 8)
  - Parker, Jane (Box 8)
  - Parrish, John & Anne (Box 8)
  - Patterson, Hugh B., Jr (Box 8)
  - Peel, Roy V (Box 8)
  - Pendleton, Marcia H (Box 8)
  - Penegar, Ken (Box 8)
  - Pelletier, Lawrence L (Box 8)
  - Percy, LeRoy (Box 8)
  - Perl, Doris (Box 8)
  - Perry, Arnold (Box 8)
  - Perry, Guerry (Box 8)
  - Perry, William D (Box 8)
  - Peters, Ellen A (Box 8)
  - Pettingill, Dwynal (Box 8)
  - Philbrook, Clarence (Box 8)
  - Phillips, Mildred C (Box 8)
  - Pierson, W.W (Box 8)
  - Pi Sigma Alpha (Box 8)
  - Plaza, Galo (Box 8)
  - Poe, Charles Aycock (Box 8)
  - Pollack, Jack Harrison (Box 8)
  - Pollack, James K (Box 8)
  - Porter, St. Francis Hotel, San Francisco, California (Box 8)
  - Porter, W.C (Box 8)
  - Powell, Dan (Box 8)
  - Poston, H.S (Box 8)
  - Poteet, Bill (Box 8)
  - Potter, Robert S (Box 8)
  - Pound, Merritt B (Box 8)
  - Poynter, Nelson (Box 8)
  - Price, Daniel O (Box 8)
  - Price, Douglas (Box 8)
  - Prothro, James W (Box 8)
  - Prouty, Tempe Newson (Box 8)
  - Public Law Committee (Columbia University) (Box 8)
  - Pullen, William R (Box 8)
  - Purks, Harris (Box 8)
  - P's (Bureau of Public Administration -Research Associate) (Box 8)
  - R-Q's (Bureau of Public Administration-Research Associate) (Box 8)
  - Randall, Henry (Box 8)
  - Range, Willard (Box 8)
  - Rankin, Robert S (Box 8)
  - Ranney, Austin (Box 8)
  - Ransom, Harry H (Box 8)
  - Rapp, William F (Box 8)
  - Ratner, Joseph (Box 8)
  - Rauers, Elizabeth Wannamaker (Box 8)
  - Rauers, John J., Jr (Box 8)
  - Ray, Donald P (Box 8)
  - Ray, Joseph M (Box 8)
  - Rayburn, Sam (Box 8)
  - Read, Nicholas C (Box 8)
  - Redfern, Leo F (Box 8)
  - Redford, Emmette S (Box 8)
  - Reed, Henry Clinton (Box 8)
  - Reed, Homer (Box 8)
  - Reed, Patricia (Box 8)
  - Board of Registrars (Box 8)
  - Reid, John (Box 8)
  - Reining, Henry (Box 8)
  - Reinstein, Jacques J (Box 8)
  - Rennie, Wesley F (Box 8)
  - Republican National Committee (Box 8)
  - Resnick, Elmer (Box 8)
  - Resch, E.A (Box 8)
  - Resch, Gloria (Box 8)
  - Reservation Clerk (Box 8)
  - Reviews, Southern Politics (Box 8)
  - Reynolds, Douglas W (Box 8)
  - Rhyne, Edwin H (Box 8)
  - Rice, Marion (Box 8)
  - Rice, Oscar (Box 8)
  - Richard, Ann Maxwell (Box 8)
  - Rickenbacker, Eddie (Box 8)
  - Riebel, John D (Box 8)
  - Riesman, David (Box 8)
  - Rights, Graham H (Box 8)
  - Rippy, Fred (Box 8)
  - Rivers, George A (Box 8)
- (Ro-So)
  - Roady, Elston (Box 9)
  - Roberts, George (Box 9)
  - Roberts, James S (Box 9)
  - Roberts, Martha McMillan (Box 9)
  - Robertson, Catherine (Box 9)
  - Robertson, J. Righton (Box 9)
  - Robertson, Joseph (Box 9)
  - Robertson Transfer Company (Box 9)
  - Robbins, Albert H (Box 9)
  - Robbins, Robert (Box 9)
  - Robson, C.B (Box 9)
  - Robson, William A (Box 9)
  - Roe, Arthur (Box 9)
  - Roger Kent Incorporated (Box 9)
  - Roger, Mims (Box 9)
  - Rollman, Heinz (Box 9)
  - Roosevelt, James M (Box 9)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Centenniel Commission (Box 9)
  - Roosevelt Unviersity (Box 9)
  - Ross, Charles Hamilton (Box 9)
  - Rothe, Marschal D., Jr (Box 9)
  - Rothrock, John (Box 9)
  - Rowe, Leonard (Box 9)
  - Rumbough, Stanley Jr (Box 9)
  - Ruml, Beardsley (Box 9)
  - Rusk, Dean (Box 9)
  - Russell, Richard B (Box 9)
  - Ruth, Robert W (Box 9)
  - Ryerson, Edward L (Box 9)
  - R's (Bureau of Public Administration) (Box 9)
  - Sady, Emil J (Box 9)
  - Sainz, Manual (Box 9)
  - Salisbury, Bob (Box 9)
  - Sanders, Marion K (Box 9)
  - Sanford, Charles S (Box 9)
  - Sanford, Terry (Box 9)
  - Sanford, Terry (Govenor) (Box 9)
  - Sanders, Sanders (Box 9)
  - Sarratt, Reed (Box 9)
  - Saunders, Sibyl Orr (Box 9)
  - Salz, Beate R (Box 9)
  - Sauerwein, Jacques (Box 9)
  - Saunders, J. Maryon (Box 9)
  - Saunders, J. Maryon (Box 9)
  - Saye, Albert B (Box 9)
  - Sayre, Wallace S (Box 9)
  - Scammon, Richard (Box 9)
  - Scarrow, Havard A (Box 9)
  - Schattschneider, E.E (Box 9)
  - Schenkkan, R.F (Box 9)
  - Schlesinger, Joseph A (Box 9)
  - Schley, Cooper Myers (Box 9)
  - Schnibben, Frances (Box 9)
  - Schrader, Margaret (Box 9)
  - Schreiber, Walter R (Box 9)
  - Scoble, Harry M (Box 9)
  - Scott, W. Kerr (Box 9)
  - Seasholes, Bradbury (Box 9)
  - Seay, W.G (Box 9)
  - Selman, J.W (Box 9)
  - Setze, Adolphus Mrs (Box 9)
  - Setze, J.A (Box 9)
  - Seymour, Hubert Jr (Box 9)
  - Shadow, Mary (Box 9)
  - Shaffer, Charles M (Box 9)
  - Shannon, Jasper B (Box 9)
  - Sharp, Martha (Box 9)
  - Shaskan, George F., Jr (Box 9)
  - Shaw, G. Howard (Box 9)
  - Shearin, P.E (Box 9)
  - Sheldon, Richard (Box 9)
  - Sheps, Cecil G (Box 9)
  - Sherrill, Basil L (Box 9)
  - Shils, Edward A (Box 9)
  - Shooshan, Harriet Gregg (Box 9)
  - Shooshan, Harry M., Jr (Box 9)
  - Short, Lloyd M (Box 9)
  - Shotts, Claude C (Box 9)
  - Shugg, Roger W (Box 9)
  - Sibley, Elbridge (Box 9)
  - Sieber, H.A (Box 9)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon (Box 9)
  - Simon, Herbert A (Box 9)
  - Simpson, George L (Box 9)
  - Simpson, William Hays (Box 9)
  - Sindler, Allan P (Box 9)
  - Skinner, Leigh (Box 9)
  - Skuce, John (Box 9)
  - Sloan, Katharine E (Box 9)
  - Smith, Mac Jr (Box 9)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 9)
  - Society of Colonial Laws (Box 9)
  - Soldier Voting Committee APSA (Box 9)
  - Soldier Voting Committee APSP (Box 9)
- (So-Un)
  - South, U.S. - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Southern, Harlan (Box 10)
  - Southern Regional Council (Box 10)
  - Southern Regional Council (Box 10)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 10)
  - Southern School News (Box 10)
  - Southwest, U.S. - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Spencer, Frank W (Box 10)
  - Stahl, Margaret C (Box 10)
  - State Department Application to 1948 (Box 10)
  - State Department for Policy, Etc., - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - State, Department of (Box 10)
  - Steele, George S (Box 10)
  - Stein, Harold (Box 10)
  - Stephenson, William A.F (Box 10)
  - Stoddard, Sanford M (Box 10)
  - Strong, Julia (Box 10)
  - Strong, Donald S (Box 10)
  - Strong, Walter H (Box 10)
  - Stern, Edgar B (Box 10)
  - Stewart, William S (Box 10)
  - Still, Samuel H., Jr (Box 10)
  - Stoll, Marion R (Box 10)
  - Strauss, Anna Lord (Box 10)
  - Street, James (Box 10)
  - Strong, Donald S (Box 10)
  - Strong, Julia (Box 10)
  - Strong, Kakie (Box 10)
  - Stroud, Virgil C (Box 10)
  - Student Faculty Judicial Review Board (Box 10)
  - Sugg, Harold (Box 10)
  - Sundkuist, James (Box 10)
  - Survey Research Center (Box 10)
  - Swanson, Thor (Box 10)
  - Swisher, Carl B (Box 10)
  - Sylvester, Harry (Box 10)
  - Smith, Harry (Box 10)
  - Smith, Helena (Box 10)
  - Smith, Lincoln (Box 10)
  - Smith, M. Brewster (Box 10)
  - Smith, McNeill (Box 10)
  - Smith, O.E., Jr (Box 10)
  - Smith, Rhoten A (Box 10)
  - Smith, Wells Hamlin (Box 10)
  - Snodgrass, Robert R (Box 10)
  - Snow, Faye W (Box 10)
  - Snyder, Richard (Box 10)
  - Spearman, Walter (Box 10)
  - Spencer, Frank W (Box 10)
  - Spingarn, Stephen J (Box 10)
  - Spruill, Corydon (Box 10)
  - State Planning Board (Box 10)
  - Stewart, Eric (Box 10)
  - Stinnett, Edith Sognier (Box 10)
  - Strong, Ormand B (Box 10)
  - Sutton, Willis A (Box 10)
  - "S" - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - S's (Bureau of Public Administration Research Associate) (Box 10)
  - Tannenbaum, Frank (Box 10)
  - Tanner, Bobo (Box 10)
  - Tarlton, William S (Box 10)
  - Income Tax, Property Tax (Box 10)
  - Taylor, Glen H (Box 10)
  - Taylor, Isaac M (Box 10)
  - TN Valley Authority (Box 10)
  - Tewksbury, Barbara (Box 10)
  - Tewksbury, Joan (Box 10)
  - Tewksbury, Howard H (Box 10)
  - Thibaut, John (Box 10)
  - Thompson, Charles A.H (Box 10)
  - Thompson, Katharine (Box 10)
  - Thompson, W.E (Box 10)
  - Thornhill, Archie J (Box 10)
  - TIME (Box 10)
  - Toompkins, Bernard (Box 10)
  - Travel Fund (Box 10)
  - Trueblood, D. Elton (Box 10)
  - Truman, David B (Box 10)
  - Tumin, Melvin (Box 10)
  - Tweedy, Mary Johnson (Box 10)
  - Tyler, Gus (Box 10)
  - Tyler, Ralph W (Box 10)
  - Tyrone, Kirby (Box 10)
  - "T" - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - T's Miscellaneous (Bureau of Public Administration) (Box 10)
  - TUV's Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Umstead, John W., Jr (Box 10)
  - UN Day - Chapel Hill (Box 10)
- (Un-Zi)
  - UNESCO (Box 11)
  - Unitarian (Box 11)
  - United Nations Day (Box 11)
  - University of North Carolina Press (Box 11)
  - University of Virginia (Box 11)
  - UNC: The Oliver Max Gardner Award (Box 11)
  - UNC: Class of 1937 Memorial Committee (Box 11)
  - UNC: A Report to the Board of Trustees "On Communism and the University" (Box 11)
  - Upton, Ann (Box 11)
  - "U" - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Vaden, H. Taylor (Box 11)
  - Vanderford, Kenneth H (Box 11)
  - Vance, Rupert B (Box 11)
  - Vancronkhite, John (Box 11)
  - Van Doren, John (Box 11)
  - Vickman, Marilyn (Box 11)
  - Vieg, John (Box 11)
  - Vaughn, Donald S (Box 11)
  - Venezuela (Box 11)
  - U's,V's - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - U's,V's (Bureau of Public Administration) (Box 11)
  - Waldo, Dwight (Box 11)
  - Walker, Elizabeth Myers (Box 11)
  - Walker, Harry J (Box 11)
  - Wallace, Earle (Box 11)
  - Wallace, H.A (Box 11)
  - Wallace, Wesley H (Box 11)
  - Wallis, Allen (Box 11)
  - Ward, Robert E (Box 11)
  - Wardle, Elizabeth C (Box 11)
  - Waring, Margaret G (Box 11)
  - Warnell, Harry (Box 11)
  - Warner, Estella (Box 11)
  - Washington & Lee University (Box 11)
  - Weaver, John C (Box 11)
  - Weeks, Edward (Box 11)
  - Weeks, O. Douglas (Box 11)
  - Weeks, Sinclair (Box 11)
  - Weinberg, Sidney J (Box 11)
  - Weiss, John K (Box 11)
  - Weiss, Samuel (Box 11)
  - Welt, Louis G (Box 11)
  - West, Langdon (Box 11)
  - Whedbee, Robert (Box 11)
  - Wheeler, John H (Box 11)
  - Whitaker, Ridley (Box 11)
  - White, Walter (Box 11)
  - Whitehall, Arthur M., Jr (Box 11)
  - Whyburn, W.M (Box 11)
  - Wilbern, York (Box 11)
  - Wilcox, L.C (Box 11)
  - Wiley, W.L (Box 11)
  - Wilkinson, Everett (Box 11)
  - Williams, Harry B (Box 11)
  - Williams, Harvey (Box 11)
  - Williams, J.A (Box 11)
  - Williamson, Harold L (Box 11)
  - Willis, Charles F., Jr (Box 11)
  - Wilson, Henry H., Jr (Box 11)
  - Wilson, Hugh (Box 11)
  - Wilson, Logan (Box 11)
  - Wilson, Louis R (Box 11)
  - Wilson, T.J., Jr (Box 11)
  - Wiltsee, Herbert L (Box 11)
  - Winslow, Rex (Box 11)
  - Wirths, Theodore W (Box 11)
  - Wisdom, John Minor (Box 11)
  - Wise, Sid (Box 11)
  - Wood, Ralford J (Box 11)
  - Woodhouse, E.J (Box 11)
  - Woodhouse, Margaret K (Box 11)
  - Woodruff, Richard V (Box 11)
  - Woodward, Stanley (Box 11)
  - Workman, W.D., Jr (Box 11)
  - World Federalist (Box 11)
  - Wynn, Earl (Box 11)
  - W's - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - W's (Bureau of Public Administration) (Box 11)
  - X - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Yale Law Journal (Box 11)
  - Yates, David W (Box 11)
  - Yeatman, Trey P (Box 11)
  - Young, John (Box 11)
  - Young, Malcolm Maclean (Box 11)
  - Young Men's Christian Association: Chapel Hill, North Carolina (Box 11)
  - Young, Robert (Box 11)
  - Young, William H (Box 11)
  - Y - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Y, Z's - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Zimmerman, Eric W (Box 11)
  - Zirkle, Mary C (Box 11)
  - X,Y,Z's - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence and Books
  - I's & J's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - J's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - H's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Q's & R's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - P's & Q's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - P's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - O's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - N's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - M's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - L's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - K's - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Key, V.O (Box 12)
  - Key, V.O. and Lu (Box 12)
  - Key, V.O. and Lu (Box 12)
  - Key, V.O (Box 12)
  - Key, V.O (Box 12)
  - M - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Book: A National Information Network: Changing Our Lives in the 21st Century
  - Book: The Flowering of New England 1815-1865 - by Van Wyck Brooks (Box 12)
  - Book: American Medicine: Challenge for the 1980's - by David E. Rogers (Box 12)
  - Book: The Magnificent Enterprise: A Chronicle of Vassar College (Box 12)
  - Book: Black Americans by John Hope Franklin (Box 12)
  - Book: Ghandi: An Autobiography (Box 12)
  - Book: The ABC Murders - by Agatha Christie (Box 12)
- Invitation Lists, Responses; Correspondence (Wedding Announcements, Christmas Cards (1976) and Birthday Cards, 1966-1988
  - Invitation Lists (Box 13)
  - Invitation Lists (Box 13)
  - Mrs. Heard (Invitations, 1973) (Box 13)
  - Calendar (12/16/79) Christmas Reception (Box 13)
  - Spring Party (Box 13)
  - 211 DPD Entertainments, November 19, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Bomb Survival Materials (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1982 & 1983 (Mostly Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1983 (Mostly Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1984 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1985 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1975 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1973 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1973 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1974 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1966 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1967 & 1968 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1970 (Wedding Response Notes) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1984 (Wedding Announcements & Postcards) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1984 (Wedding Announcements & Postcards) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1986 & 1987 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1976 (Wedding Announcements & Christmas Cards) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1976 (Wedding Announcements & Christmas Cards) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1972 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1980 (Wedding Announcements) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: 1988 (Alex's Birthday Cards & Wrapping Paper) (Box 13)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous (Includes Francis Robinson Exhibition Program) (Box 13)
  - Speech: Alexander Heard ;Given to Conference of Deans of Southern Graduate Schools, Oak Ridge, Tennessee, November 26, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Report: To: Helen Hill Miller, From: Alexander Heard, (Private Copy) (Box 14)
  - Newspaper/Journal Articles: Mostly re: Alexander Heard (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - Invitation Lists (Box 14)
  - Assorted Magazines (Box 14)
  - Manilla Envelopes: Includes Vanderbilt Materials, Blair School of Music Materials & Newspaper Clippings (1960's) (Box 14)
  - Correspondence: Miscellanous (Includes Letters, Christmas Cards, Receipts, Invitation Responses, Etc.) (Box 14)
  - Inaugural Invitation: Lyndon B. Johnson, January 20, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Tourist/Historical Materials: Savannah, Georgia (Early 1960's) (Manilla Envelope) (Box 14)
  - Manuscript: Rough Draft - by Sophie Aberle, Parts I,II,III,IV & Summary (1978) (Work with United States Indian Reservations, 1927-76) (Box 14)
- Newspapers And Magazines, 1973-1979
  - Newspaper Articles: Re: Alexander Heard, 1973-79 (Box 15)
  - Magazines: Politics (Watergate, etc.), 1974-79 (Box 15)
- The American Assembly
  - Books: United States Government Congressional Hearings, 81st Congress, 2nd Session and 82nd Congress, 1st Session (8 articles) (Box 16)
  - Publication: State Legislatures in American Politics (The 29th American Assembly, Columbia University) (Box 16)
  - Notebooks: State Legislatures in American Politics (Rough Draft) (2 Articles) (Box 16)
  - American Assembly Papers: State Legislatures in American Politics (Box 16)
  - Rough Draft: State Legislatures in American Politics (7 Articles) (Box 16)
  - A.A. (Back Papers) (Box 16)
  - American Assembly (Action) (The 29th American Assembly) (Box 16)
  - The American Assembly (April 28-May 1, 1966; Arden House, New York) (Box 16)
  - American Assembly (Box 16)
- Ford Foundation Papers
  - Draft: 25-Year Review Paper; The Ford Foundation, "Philanthropic Choices, Style and Methods: (Box 17)
  - A 25-Year Review" (February 20, 1976) (Includes one note of corrections and one letter, To: McGeorge Bundy, From: Richard Magat, February 23, 1976) (Black 3-Ring Notebook) (Box 17)
  - Student Letters: To: Mr. & Mrs. Alexander Heard, April/May 1963 (Box 17)
  - Papers: (Analytic Commentaries) Board of Trustees Future Program Planning Project (Box 17)
  - Publication: The Ford Foundation; Board of Trustees Furture Program Planning Project (Summary of Discussions) (June 24 &25, 1976) (Includes Working Draft: "Priority Areas for the Ford Foundation in the Nineteen Eighties," Etc.) (Box 17)
  - Publication: Board of Trustees Meeting, "Schedule of Events and Related Reading" (Phoenix, June 27, 1984) (Box 17)
  - Publication: Board of Trustees Meeting, "Schedule of Events and Related Reading for Community College and Arizona Farmworkers Visits" (Phoenix, June 28, 1984) (Box 17)
  - Publication: Board of Trustees Meeting, "Schedule of Events and Related Reading for Water Visit" (Phoenix, June 28, 1984) (Box 17)
  - Publication: Board of Trustees Meeting, "Schedule of Events and Related Reading" (Santa Fe, June 30, 1984) (Box 17)
  - Correspondence: Ford Foundation (Box 17)
  - Correspondence: Ford Foundation (Box 17)
  - Correspondence: Ford Foundation (Box 17)
  - Correspondence: Ford Foundation (Box 17)
  - Audit Committee (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Ford Foundation): Papers, Notes & Newspaper Clippings, 1975, 1976 (Box 17)
  - Future (Box 17)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 17)
  - Ford (Box 17)
  - FF Futures Papers (Box 17)
  - Papers: Ford Foundation (Includes one letter, March 9, 1976), March 1976 (Box 17)
  - Papers: Ford Foundation, March 1976 (Box 17)
  - Papers: Ford Foundation, March 1976 (Box 17)
  - Papers: Ford Foundation, March 1976 (Box 17)
  - Publication (Ford Foundation): "Current Interests of the Ford Foundation 1976 & 1977" (Box 17)
  - 1976 Meeting (Box 17)
  - Ford: Special Meeting (Box 17)
  - Publication: "Directory of Scheduled Donors" (Ford Foundation of Trustees/Future Program Planning Project/1976) (Box 17)
  - Publication: "Staff Responses to Alexander Heard's September 24 Memorandum: Next Steps in Planning for the Foundation's Future" ,Volumes I & II (Ford Foundation Board of Trustees/ Future Program Planning Project/1976) (Box 17)
  - Publication: "A Response to the Trustees on Proposed Priorities, Special Questions, and Remaining Hard Choices" - by McGeorge Bundy (Ford Foundation of Trustees/ Future Program Planning Project/1976) (Box 17)
  - Democratic National Committee: Partisan Campaign Material (Box 18)
  - Money Ledger (Legal Pad) (Box 18)
  - Instruction: 3rd Nat'l. Acct (Box 18)
  - Records of Monthly Mail, 1975,1978,1979,1980,1981)(Black Vanderbilt Notebook (Box 18)
  - Postage Stamps (Box 18)
  - Calendars of Events: Alexander Heard, 1959,1960,1961,1962,1963,1981,1982 (Box 18)
  - Calendar/Itinerary/Travel Plan Schedules: Alexander Heard, 1982 & 1982 (Box 18)
  - Montauk Conference on the Presidential Selection Process, Auagust 1-7, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Curriculum Vitae: Bruce, S.S.(Sinclair-Smith), August 20, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Receipts, 1980 & 1982 (Box 18)
  - New York Herald Tribune: "A-Test Bomb on Christmas Island" (May 27, 1962) and "Stocks Rebound" (Stock Exchange), May 30, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous: Papers, Correspondence (Includes Student Political Science 52 Exam) (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous: Address Cards (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous: Folders, Blank Paper, Envelopes (Box 18)
  - Daily Calendars: Alexander Heard, 1952,1954,1956,1958,1958-59,December 1959, January-December 1960, 1961,1962,1963 (Box 18)
  - Microfilm: Two Unbound Manuscripts - by Mrs. Philip Thorton, "Down Again, Up Again" and "Tune & Lay"(?) (Box 18)
  - Name Tags: /Alexander Heard (Box 18)
  - Note Cards: Cross-Referenced Addresses (Box 18)
  - MSS: Nominations (Introduction, Earlier Drafts) (Box 1)